# Joaquín Mesa

Buenos Aires, Argentina  $\cdot$  joacomesa@gmail.com  $\cdot$  Linkedin: Joaquín Mesa  $\cdot$  Portfolio: joacomesa.com.ar

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

Front-end developer with a focus on UX and advanced Digital Communication student. My skills as a developer are complemented by my knowledge in design and user experience. Also, artificial intelligence has become a fundamental tool in my professional life. I am a consistent, resourceful, and self-taught person who enjoys teamwork and am always open to learn new skills and technologies.

## **SKILLS**

**Technologies**: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Sass,

Astro, Next JS, SQL, PHP

Tools: GitHub, Git,Others: UX / UI Design, Wireframing,Firebase, Figma,Prototyping, SEO

Photoshop, Wordpress Languages: Spanish, English (C1 IELTS)

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Project Management Internship - Delateral

roject management internemp 2 clatera

Trainee role

- Collaboration in branding, communication and digital marketing projects
- Websites and web platforms management
- Weekly meetings with the team and clients

## **Assistant Professor** - University of Palermo

In two subjects:

Digital Production III (Web Development | HTML - CSS - JS - PHP - SQL) - Prof. Mariano Ingerto Interactive Communication III (UX / UI Design) - Prof. Álvaro Ghisolfo

- Professor assistance,
- Lesson planning
- Student support with coding and design projects

# Freelance Web Developer & Designer

January 2023 - Present

August 2023 - Present

**December 2023 - Present** 

- Web interface designing in Figma
- Development, deployment and maintenance of accesible, scalable and responsive websites
- Communication with clients

Data Entry - Fundación Kaleidos

December 2021 - January 2021

- Data entry in Wordpress
- Microsoft Excel
- Multimedia searching, selecting and editing

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor's Degree in Digital Communication** 

University of Palermo 2021 - Present

## **COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION**



Front-end React Development Coderhouse



**UX / UI Specialization**California Institute of Arts - Coursera